This kitty is Mittens. This one is Fitzhugh.
这只小猫叫手套 这只是费修
And this little guy in the cat condo is Jinkies.
然后这住在猫公寓的小男生是金吉
That's a lot of cats, Jo Lynn.
好多猫喔，裘琳
Single, are you?
你是单身吧？
- I'll get it. - Okay.
-我来接 -好啊！
Chandler Bing.
钱德宾
How come you're answering your own phone? Where's your crazy assistant?
为什么你是自己接电话呢？ 你的疯狂助理去哪了？
You're not crazy. You're not crazy.
你没有疯，你没有疯
Otherwise, why would you have all those cats?
否则你怎么会养那么多只猫呢？
What's up, Joe?
什么事，乔伊？
What have we always wanted to do together?
有什么事是我们一直想要一起做的？
Braid each other's hair and ride horseback on the beach?
帮彼此编辫子然后在海边骑马吗？
No. No. No. When you get home tomorrow night..
不不不，你明晚回家时…
you and I are gonna be at the Wizards-Knicks game, courtside!
你跟我要去看巫师队对尼克队球赛 场边座位！
- Courtside? Oh, my God! - Yeah!
-场边座位？喔！我的天啊！ -是啊！
Maybe Michael Jordan will dive for the ball and break my jaw with his knee!
或许麦可乔登会扑过来抢球 然后用他的膝盖撞断我的下巴！
That is so cool. I'll let Monica know.
真是太酷了，我来告诉摩妮卡
These need your signature.
这些需要你的签名
Listen, Jo Lynn, that was my friend Joey. He calls everybody crazy.
听着，裘琳，那是我朋友乔伊 他总是叫每个人疯狂的
- Hello? - Hey, hon, it's me.
-哈？ -嘿，亲爱的，是我
Hi. How's the crazy cat lady?
嘿，那个疯狂猫女人还好吗？
Joey just called.
乔伊刚打电话来…
He's got courtside Knicks tickets for him and me tomorrow night.
他帮我买到了明晚 尼克队比赛的场边座位
But tomorrow night's the only night I get off from the restaurant.
但是明晚是我唯一不用上班的晚上
If you go, we won't have a night together for a week.
如果你去看球赛 我们会有一星期没有办法在一起
But honey, it's courtside! The cheerleaders will be right in..
但是亲爱的，那是场边座位！ 啦啦队会就在正前…
That's not the way to convince you.
这不是说服你的好方式
I don't wanna be one of those wives that says:
我不想要成为那种老婆 老是说：
"You can't go to the game. You have to spend time with me."
“你不能去看球赛，你要陪我”
So if you could just realize it on your own..
所以如果你自己能够有认知…
I know. You're right. I wanna see you too.
我知道，你说的对 我也想要见到你
I gotta figure out a way to tell Joey. He's looking forward to it.
我得要想想要怎么告诉乔伊 他是满心期待着
Tell him you haven't seen your wife in a long time.
告诉他你很久没有见到老婆了
Tell him that having a long-distance relationship is really difficult.
告诉他长距离关系是很难维系的
Tell him that what little time we have together is precious.
告诉他 我们这些有限的相处时间是很宝贵的
I'll think of something.
我会想想别的
The One With Rachel's Phone Number
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
You look..
你看起来…
I mean, it's just.. That dress..
我是说，这真的… 这件洋装…
Well, I hope the ends of these sentences are good.
嗯，我希望那句话的结尾是正面的
They're good. It's just been a while since I've seen you like this.
是好的，只是我很久没有 看到你这样打扮
You clean up good.
你产后恢复的真好
Really? Well, thank you.
真的吗？ 喔，谢谢你
Okay, stop looking at me like that.
好了，别再这样看着我了
- Last time that happened, that happened. - Right, right.
-上次这样的时候，就那样了 -对，是的
So are you excited about your first night away from Emma?
你很高兴你第一次可以离开艾犸 晚上出去玩吗？
Yeah, yeah. Phoebe and l are gonna have so much fun.
是啊，菲比跟我会玩的很开心的
- Thank you for watching the baby. - It's fine.
-谢谢你帮我看小孩 -不用客气
Actually, I invited Mike over.
事实上，我有邀请麦克过来
- Phoebe's Mike? - Yeah.
-菲比的麦克吗？ -是啊
- I didn't know you hung out. - We don't..
-我不知道你们很熟 -我们没有…
but I'd like to get to know him.
但是我想要多认识他
Maybe have a little dinner, drinks, conversation.
或许用点晚餐，喝点酒然后聊聊天
That's so cute. Ross and Mike's first date.
好纯真可爱 罗斯跟麦克的第一次约会
It's not a date.
这不是约会
But if it turns out to be something more..
但是如果发展成更进一步的关系…
I'll leave a tie on the door.
我会在门把上绑带子
Will that be awkward? What are you gonna talk about?
那会不会很尴尬呢？ 你们要聊些什么呢？
I don't know. But you know, we have a lot in common, you know?
我不知道，但是你知道的 我们有许多共同点，你知道吗？
He plays piano. I played keyboards in college.
他会弹钢琴，我在大学弹过键盘
He's been divorced. I have some experience in that area.
他离过婚，我在那方面也有些经验
- Yeah? - Hi!
-是吗？ -嗨！
Girl's night out indeed.
果真是女人之夜
So I think Emma is probably down for the night..
我想艾犸今晚可能已经睡了…
- but if you need anything.. - We'll be fine.
-但是如果你们需要… -我们会没事的
- You go have fun. - Okay, you too.
-祝你们玩得愉快 -好的，你们也是
- Thanks. - And I hope you score.
-谢谢 -还有我希望你可以上垒得分
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.
-好的，再见 -再见
So, welcome.
嗯，欢迎
- I got beer. - I got bottled breast milk.
-我有啤酒 -我有瓶装母乳
- Why don't we start with the beer. - Okay.
-我看我们先喝啤酒好了 -好的
- So Phoebe tells me you play piano. - Yeah.
-菲比告诉我你会弹钢琴 -是啊
You know, I used to play keyboards in college.
我在大学的时候也会弹键盘
Do you have one here?
你这里有吗？
No.
没有
Okay.
好的
You know, I'm divorced.
你知道的，我离过婚…
Phoebe.. Phoebe says you're.. You've been divorced?
菲比…菲比…说你… 你也离过婚？
Yeah, yeah.
是的，是啊
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't really like to talk about it.
很抱歉，我真的不太喜欢谈那件事
That's okay. We'll talk about something else.
没关系，我们可以聊别的
- This is a nice apartment. - Thanks.
-这间公寓蛮不错的 -谢谢
The moldings are all original.
这些装饰条板都是原来就有的
I don't know if the moldings are original in my apartment.
我不知道我公寓的装饰条板 是不是原创的？
- So you're a paleontologist, right? - Yeah.
-你是古生物学家，是吗？ -是啊
My cousin's a paleontologist.
我表哥也是古生物学家
Well, he and I would probably have a lot to talk about.
嗯，他跟我可能会有较多话题可以聊
- Welcome home. - Well, look at you.
-欢迎回家 -嗯，瞧瞧你
Yeah. What do you think?
是啊，觉得怎样呢？
Well, it looks great. It's just..
嗯，看起来很棒，只不过…
I'm wearing the same thing underneath, so..
我里面穿的也跟你一样，所以…
You see what I mean?
你知道我的意思吗？
Hey! How come your door's locked?
嘿！为什么你的门是锁着的？
- Just a second! - No, no, no!
-等一下！ -不不不！
- Joey can't know I'm here. - Why not?
-乔伊不能看到我在这里 -为什么不能？
I didn't want to say I couldn't go to the game..
我不知道怎么告诉他 我不能去看球赛…
- so I told him I had to stay in Tulsa. - So you lied to him?
-所以我跟他说我得要留在土尔沙 -所以你跟他说谎？
It's always better to lie than to have the complicated discussion.
说谎比费口舌解释要好太多了
Except with you.
除了跟你之外
Hey, open the door! What's going on?
嘿，开门！是怎么回事？
- What are you..? - Hi.
-你是在干么？ -嗨
Why are you dressed like that?
你为什么穿成这样呢？
Because Chandler's gonna be home in a couple of days..
因为钱德几天以后就要回来了…
so I thought I would just, you know, practice the art of seduction.
所以我想可以 先练习一下妩媚的技巧
I thought I heard a man's voice before.
我刚刚好像有听到男人的声音
No, I was just doing Chandler's side of the conversation.
没有，我只是在扮演钱德说话
You know, like, "Hi, how do I look?"
你知道的，就像是： “嗨，我看起来如何？”
"Really sexy. Could I be any more turned on?" You know?
“真性感，我还能比现在更兴奋吗？” 你知道的
Okay. Wait a minute.
好的，等一下
Why are there two glasses of wine out?
为什么有两杯酒呢？
Because one of them is for you!
因为一杯是要给你的
Cheers! Okay, bye-bye.
干杯！好了，再见
You know, it's funny. I've been practicing the art of seduction myself.
真好玩，我自己也一直 在练习勾引的技巧
- You might wanna keep practicing. - Yeah.
-你最好再继续加强练习 -是喔！
- It's Joey. - What?
-是乔伊 -什么？
- Hey, Joe. - Dude, come home!
-嘿，乔伊 -老兄，回家！
- What? Why? - Come home!
-什么？为什么？ -回家！
Look, I can't. What's going on?
听着，我不行，是怎么回事呢？
I don't know how to tell you this, but I think Monica's cheating on you!
我不知道要怎么开口 但是我想摩妮卡背着你劈腿！
I told you, you shouldn't have married someone hotter than you!
早就告诉过你，你不应该娶一个 比你辣那么多的人！
If you can't deal with this, then I'm gonna.
如果你没有办法回来处理这种事 那我去处理
- No! - I just heard him!
-不！ -我听到他的声音了！
Can you hear him now?
你现在有听到他的声音吗？
No. All right, I'm going in.
没有，好了，我要进去了
- No, wait! - I heard him again!
-不，等等！ -我又听到他了！
All right, just stay there. I'm coming home.
好了，你就待在那里别动 我要回家了
I'll see you when you get here.
等你回来的时候见
I'll wait out in the hall in case he comes out.
我会在门外守着以免他走了
- Is that really necessary? - Absolutely. You'd do it for me.
-有那个必要吗？ -当然，你也会为我这样做的
Not that you ever have to, because I know how to keep my women satisfied.
不是说你会有机会那样做 因为我知道要如何满足我的女人
- Yeah, listen, thanks a lot. - Okay, bye.
-是啊，听着，万分感谢 -好了，再见
He thinks I'm a slut.
他认为我是淫荡的女人
Oh, right, and you're supposed to be a fireman?
喔，对了 你不是应该当义勇消防队员的吗？
Shouldn't the pizza be here by now?
披萨不是早就该到了吗？
I mean, they said 30 minutes or less. Well, how long has it been?
我是说，他们说不用三十分钟就会到 已经多久了呢？
Eleven minutes.
十一分钟
And now 12.
现在是十二分钟
- So you wanna watch TV? - You think I haven't thought of that?
-那你想看电视吗？ -你以为我没有想过吗？
I mean, I would like to but the cable's out.
我也想啊，但是第四台断了
Didn't seem like such a big deal until tonight.
本来不觉得有什么大不了的，直到今晚
- So you like the beer? - I do. I do.
-你喜欢这啤酒吗？ -是的，我喜欢
Although, it's actually a lager.
不过，这事实上是淡啤酒
What's the difference between beer and lager?
那啤酒跟淡啤酒有什么不同呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
We could look it up.
我们可以查一查
Things are about to get wild.
真是越来越有趣了
Oh, God, remember the girls' nights we used to have..
喔，天啊 还记得以前的女生之夜我们…
sitting around talking about you and Ross?
坐在一起讨论你跟罗斯的事吗？
Oh, God! It seems like forever ago.
喔！天啊！感觉好像是上辈子的事
I know.
我知道
So, what's going on with you and Ross?
那，你跟罗斯是怎样了呢？
Well, I don't know. I mean, for a long time, nothing.
喔，我不知道，我是说 已经很久没有怎样了
But you know, actually, right before you picked me up..
但是，事实上 就在你来接我之前…
Ross and I had a little thing.
罗斯跟我有个小小的“插曲”
Oh, my God! I love things! What happened?
喔！我的天！我最爱小插曲！ 发生什么事？
Well, first he told me he liked how I looked.
嗯，他先是告诉我 他喜欢我看起来的样子
And then we had a little..
然后我们做了个小小的…
eye contact.
眼神交换
Eye contact?
眼神交换？
I hope you were using protection.
我希望你们有用避孕措施
Excuse me, these are from the two gentlemen at the end of the bar.
不好意思 这些是吧台最后那两位先生请的
Oh, actually, I can't have another one on account of my breast milk.
喔，事实上 因为喂母乳的关系我不能多喝一杯
Okay.
好的
Hey, Rach, maybe there's a less disgusting way to decline a drink.
嘿，瑞秋，有没有比较不恶心的理由 可以让你不喝酒的
Should we send them something back? Let's send them mashed potatoes!
我们应该回请他们什么吗？ 我们请他们吃马铃薯泥好了！
No, wait! Don't do that!
不，等等！别那么做！
That'll make them think they can come over.
那样他们就会认为他们可以过来
So, what if they do?
所以呢？过来又如何呢？
We're not here to meet guys. You have a boyfriend. I have a baby and a Ross.
我们不是来这里钓男人的 你有男友，我有小孩还有罗斯
Yeah, but nothing has to happen. We're just having fun.
是啊，但这只是好玩 又不会发生什么事
You know, not everything has to go as far as eye contact.
你知道的 不是每件事都得发展到眼神交换地步的
Chandler, you have to tell Joey you're not in Tulsa.
钱德，你得要告诉乔伊你不在土尔沙
Isn't it better for him to think you're cheating on me..
让他认为是你在欺骗我…
than for him to think I'm cheating on him?
总比他认为我在欺骗他好吧？
I heard it.
我自己听到了
I don't want him to think I'm having an affair.
我不想让他误会我有外遇
All right, I've got a plan. I'll go down the fire escape..
好了，我有个计划 我会从防火梯爬下去…
Because all good plans start with, "I'll go down the fire escape."
所有完美的计划都是从 “我会从防火梯爬下去”开始的
Hear me out, woman!
听我说完，女人！
I'll go down the fire escape and wait.
我会从防火梯爬下去然后等着
Then it'll be like I just got back from Tulsa.
然后就会像是我刚从土尔沙回来一样…
Joey and I will come in and see that there's no guy in here.
然后乔伊跟我进来 看到这里根本没有男人
Aren't you afraid that Joey's gonna figure all this out?
你难道不怕乔伊会识破吗？
I heard it.
我自己听到了
- I'm gonna wait. - The scary pigeon's back?
-我要等一下 -可怕的鸽子又回来了吗？
It's huge.
超大的
I can't believe you live in that building. My grandmother lives in that building!
我不敢相信你住在那栋公寓 我奶奶也住在那栋公寓！
Ida Greene? No sense of personal space..
艾达葛林，没有个人空间感…
kind of smells like chicken, looks like a potato.
闻起来像鸡，看起来像马铃薯
- "Spuds" is your grandmother? - That's my bubbe!
-“洋芋”是你奶奶？ -那就是我“啊嬷”！
So we're on our way to a couple of parties.
我们要再去几个派对
Maybe we could get your numbers and call if we find something fun?
或许我们可以跟你们要号码 如果遇到好玩的，打电话给你们
Yeah. I'm sorry, we weren't really looking for anything to happen..
我很抱歉，我们并没有在找什么对象
with you guys. I have a boyfriend.
我有男朋友了
- All right. - It's no big deal.
-好的 -没关系
Just out of curiosity, which one of you was for me?
只是好奇，你们哪一个喜欢我呢？
- That would've been me. - Nice.
-是我 -很好
Different situation, cowboy, and you would've had yourself a handful.
如果情况不同，小子 你可是会有得忙的
So she has a boyfriend. What is your situation?
所以她有男朋友 那你的情形是怎样呢？
Well, it's complicated. I don't actually have a boyfriend, but..
嗯，这有点复杂 我并没有男朋友，但是…
Then can I have your number?
那我可以跟你要电话号码吗？
I'm sorry, no.
我很抱歉，不行
Okay.
好的
Oh, sure!
喔，当然可以！
Oh, my God, you're giving your real number!
喔！天啊，你给他的电话是真的！
Okay, thanks. I'll give you a call later tonight.
好的，谢谢，我今晚会打给你
- Great. - Bye.
-太好了 -再见
Bye.
再见
So that's great.
那真的太棒了
You, Bill, Ross and Emma are gonna be so happy together.
你、比尔、罗斯、还有艾犸 会很快乐在一起
What were you thinking?
你是在想什么呢？
I don't know. He was cute, and he liked me. It was an impulse.
我不知道，他很可爱然后又喜欢我 我冲动之下就给他了
Like when I bought these shoes. They were cute and they liked me too.
就像我买这双鞋的时候 它们很可爱而且也喜欢我
But what about Ross? What about your moment?
那罗斯怎么办吗？你们的小插曲呢？
We had a moment. We looked at each other.
我们是有过小插曲 我们对看了彼此
Maybe if we live together for another 10 years, we may hold hands!
或许如果我们一起住了十年 我们可能就会牵手了！
But you were really excited about it.
但是你原本对这件事 是非常高兴的
- Don't you wanna talk to him? - No.
-你不想要跟他谈吗？ -不想
No, because I know exactly how the conversation's gonna go.
不想，因为我完全知道 谈话的结果会是怎样
"Hey, Ross, you know, I think we had a moment before."
“嘿！罗斯，我认为我们 刚刚有个小插曲”
"Yeah. Me too."
“是啊，我也这么认为”
"Well, but I'm not sure I really want to do anything about it."
“嗯，但是我不太确定 我是不是想再更进一步”
"Yeah. Me neither."
“是啊，我也不确定”
"Should we just live together..
我们是不是就住在一起…
and not tell each other how we're feeling?"
然后不要告诉彼此 我们互相的感受？
"Yeah, that works for me."
“是啊，我没意见”
Yeah, I see what you mean.
是啊，我知道你的意思
By the way, nice Ross imitation.
对了，你模仿的罗斯真像
Your Rachel wasn't whiny enough.
你模仿的瑞秋 不够爱发牢骚
- Well.. Hey! - Better.
-嗯…嘿！ -好多了
The point is maybe I should just stop waiting around for moments with Ross.
重点是我或许应该停止等待 跟罗斯之间的小插曲
You know? I should just move on with my life.
你知道吗？我应该要过我自己的生活了
So really, you're moving on from Ross?
真的，你要放弃罗斯了？
I don't know. Do I have to decide right now?
我不知道，我得要现在做决定吗？
You kind of just did. That guy is gonna call you tonight.
你好像已经做了 那男的今晚会打电话给你
Ross will pick up the phone, and that's a pretty clear message.
罗斯会接起电话，这是挺明白的讯息了
Oh, my God, Ross!
喔！天啊，罗斯！
Ross is gonna pick up the phone.
罗斯会接起电话
I have to get my number back. Oh, my God, he's gone!
我得拿回我的电话号码 喔！天啊，他走了！
"Oh, I have to get my number back! Oh, my God! He's gone!" Dead on.
“我得拿回我的电话号码 喔！天啊，他走了！”模仿的真棒
- You know, I'm gonna take off. - So soon?
-我想我该走了 -这么快吗？
- Yeah. - Okay.
-是啊 -好的
Well, thanks.. Thanks for the beer.
嗯，谢谢你带啤酒过来
- You mean lager? - Yeah. Good times.
-你是说淡啤酒吧？ -是啊，快乐时光
- Okay. - All right.
-好的 -好了
- Hello? - Hey, Mike, it's me.
-哈？ -嘿，麦克，是我
Listen, is.. Is Ross near you?
听着，罗斯在你旁边吗？
No, I just left.
没有，我才刚走
And that, right there, is the most interesting conversation I've had all night.
而现在，是我今晚 有过最有趣的对话了
Really? Okay.
真的吗？好的
Well, you have to go back in.
嗯，你得要再回去
What? Go back? To the land where time stands still?
什么？回去？回到时光暂停之地吗？
I'm so sorry, honey, but..
我很抱歉，亲爱的，但是…
Okay, Rachel gave this guy her number..
瑞秋给了一个男的她的电话…
and she doesn't want Ross to answer the phone.
她不希望罗斯去接电话
So you have to intercept all his calls.
所以你必须要拦截他所有的电话
I can't do that!
我不能这样做！
- He says he can't do that. - Give me the phone.
-他说他不能那样做 -电话给我
Hi, Mike. Hi, listen, I know that this is a lot to ask, but you know what?
麦克，听着，我知道这个要求很过分 但是你知道吗？
If you do this, Phoebe will do anything you want.
如果你照做 菲比会做一切你想要她做的事
- Seriously, I'm talking dirty stuff. - All right. Thank you. Hello?
-真的，我说得是很下流的事 -好了，谢谢，哈？
Hi, I'm sorry about her. But actually, she wasn't wrong about the dirty stuff.
嗨，我替她道歉，但事实上 关于下流的事，她说的没错
All right, I'll do it.
好了，我照做
But really, how much dirtier can it get?
但说真的，会有多下流呢？
Oh, Mike.
喔，麦克
Bye.
拜拜
Hey, buddy.
嘿，老兄
Hi.
嗨
- Can I come back in? - Why?
-我可以回来吗？ -为什么？
Well, I was just thinking about how much more we have to talk about.
嗯，我只是在想我们 还有很多东西可以聊
But you left.
但是你走了
That didn't take long.
那倒是挺快的
I thought you said Tulsa was, like, a three-hour flight?
我以为你说土尔沙到这里要飞三小时
Well, you're forgetting about the time difference.
嗯，你忘了把时差算进去了
- You ready? I'm gonna go in there with you. - Thanks.
-你准备好了吗？我跟你一起进去 -谢谢
Just in case there's more than one dude in there.
以防里面不只有一个男的
- Again, thanks. - Yeah.
-再一次谢谢你 -是啊
Chandler, you're home!
钱德，你回来了！
That's right! Your husband's home! So now the sex can stop!
没错！你老公回来了！ 所以现在性爱派对可以停止了！
You know what I mean.
你知道我在说什么
What are you saying?
你是在说什么？
Joey said you're here with another man!
乔伊说你跟另一个男人在一起！
There's no man in here! How dare you accuse me of that!
这里根本没有男人！ 你怎么敢这样诬赖我！
All right. Then maybe you won't mind if me and my friend take a look around.
好了，那或许你不介意 我和我的“朋友”到处看看
He can't even see us!
他根本搞不清楚状况！
- I kind of liked it. - Me too.
-我蛮喜欢这样的 -我也是
What's he doing?
他在做什么？
I arranged some pillows on the bed to look like a guy.
我用枕头做成人形在床上
Bedroom's clear. Although you might need some new pillows.
卧室没有人 不过你们可能需要换新的枕头了
All right, well, I'll check the guest room.
好了，那我去检查客房
Why do I smell men's cologne?
我为什么有闻到男人的古龙水味？
I think that's you.
我想那是你的味道
Oh, yeah. I rubbed a magazine on myself earlier.
喔，对喔，我刚刚才用 杂志磨擦到自己身上
There's nobody here, Joe.
里面没有人，乔伊
I guess not.
我想也没有
I can't believe you thought I was cheating. You owe me an apology.
我不敢相信你认为我会劈腿 你要对我道歉
- You're right. I'm so sorry. - It's an honest mistake.
-你说的对，我很抱歉 -这是出自好意的误会
It could happen to anybody. See you.
可能发生在任何人身上的，再见
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下
If you just got back from Tulsa, how did your suitcase beat you here?
如果你才刚从土尔沙回来 你的行李怎么会比你先到？
I climbed down the fire escape, and you can't put that in the closet?
我从防火梯爬了下去 而你就不能把这个藏到衣橱里吗？
So, with the exception of the fermentation process..
所以，除了发酵过程不同之外…
beer and ale are basically the same thing.
啤酒跟麦酒基本上是相同的东西
Fascinating, isn't it?
真引人入胜，不是吗？
Maybe you should look up "fascinating."
或许你应该查一下“引人入胜”
I'll get it!
我来接！
Hello? Ross' place. Mike speaking.
哈？罗斯家，我是麦克
It's for you.
要找你的
I don't understand what just happened here.
我不懂刚刚发生的事
What's going on?
是怎么回事？
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I told you I was in Tulsa because I wanted to spend the night with Monica..
我会跟你说我在土尔沙是因为 今晚我想要跟摩妮卡在一起…
and I didn't know.. I didn't think you'd understand.
而我不知道… 我以为你会不谅解
You think I'm too dumb to understand a husband needs to be with his wife?
你以为我笨到会不谅解 老公想要跟老婆在一起吗？
You think I'm, like..
你以为我就像…
- Joey? - Yeah.
-乔伊？ -怎样
I don't know what to say. We shouldn't have lied to you.
我不知道该说什么 我们不应该欺骗你的
I feel so bad. Is there anything I can do to make it up to you?
我觉得很难过，我能做什么补偿你吗？
You could go to the game with me. Even though you said you couldn't.
你可以跟我一起去看球赛 虽然你说了你不行
But then you lied to me and tricked me and gave me a bump on the head.
但是你欺骗我 然后又害我头肿了一包
I'm sorry, that's the one thing I can't do. I promised I'd be with Monica.
我很抱歉，这是我唯一无法做到的 我答应摩妮卡要跟她在一起了
All right.
好吧
- You can go. - What?
-你去吧 -什么？
You should go to the game. It's okay. I want you to.
你应该去看球赛，没关系，我要你去
- Really? You gonna be okay? - Yeah, I'll be fine.
-真的？你没关系吗？ -是的，我没关系
You know, maybe I'll stay here and practice the art of seduction.
你知道的，或许我可以留在这里 然后练习一下勾引的技巧
- You're gonna put sweats on and clean. - It's gonna be so hot!
-你要换上运动服然后打扫吧 -一定会很性感撩人！
- Bye. - Bye.
-拜 -拜
Thanks.
谢了
Here's your ticket.
你的外套拿去
Thanks. Hey, listen..
谢了，嘿，听着…
I'm never gonna lie to you again, okay?
我再也不会跟你说谎了，好吗？
And I want you to know that nobody thinks you're stupid.
而且我要你知道没有人认为你是愚蠢的
Thanks, man.
谢了，老兄
- Where you going? - Game's tomorrow night, Joe.
-你要去哪？ -球赛是明晚，乔伊
I'm glad I got to talk to your mom. She sounds nice.
我很高兴跟你妈说到话 她听起来人不错
Yeah, she's a peach.
是啊，她人很好
Oh, God!
喔！天啊！
So glad you're back!
真高兴你们回来了！
So, what did you guys do?
那你们做了些什么呢？
You know, we just drank some beer.
你知道的，我们喝了一些啤酒
Mike played with the boundaries of normal social conduct.
麦克示范了正常社交礼仪的界线在哪
It's true, I did.
是真的，我做得很好
- Well, goodbye. - Okay.
-好了，再见 -好的
- Bye. That was fun, Phoebe. - I know. It was fun.
-拜，真好玩，菲比 -我知道，真好玩
See you, guys.
再见！
Lock the door! Lock the door, seriously.
锁门！锁门，快点
Shoot, I forgot to pay Phoebe for the drinks.
糟了，我忘记给菲比酒钱了
Wait, wait. Wait, sorry. Did he call? Did that guy call?
等等，等一下，不好意思 他有打来吗？那个男的有打来吗？
No, just his mom.
没有，只有他妈打来
Around 8:30?
在八点半左右吗？
- Yeah. - Then again at 9:00?
-是的 -然后九点再一通吗？
Yeah.
是的
Hello?
哈？
No, she's not here right now. Can I take a message?
她现在不在，要留言吗？
Bill from the bar?
酒吧认识的比尔？
Okay, Bill from the bar, I'll make sure she gets your number.
好的，酒吧认识的比尔 我会把你的号码给她的
So.. So how was it?
好玩吗？
Did you guys..? You guys have a good time?
你们有…？ 你们玩的开心吗？
We had so much fun. It felt so good to be out.
我们玩的很开心，出去玩真是快乐
Rach?
瑞秋？
Yeah?
什么事呢？
Never mind.
没事
- Hey, you guys. - Hey!
-嗨，你们 -嘿！
I'll be right back. I gotta go to the bathroom.
马上回来，我要去上厕所
Stout. That's a kind of beer.
黑啤酒也是啤酒的一种